<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>LexCrypt</title><link>https://benjipeng.github.io/common-law</link><description>Where Technology Meets Common Law: Decoding Legal Principles for the Digital Age</description><copyright>LexCrypt</copyright><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://github.githubassets.com/favicons/favicon.svg</url><title>avatar</title><link>https://benjipeng.github.io/common-law</link></image><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:38:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><managingEditor>LexCrypt</managingEditor><ttl>60</ttl><webMaster>LexCrypt</webMaster><item><title>LexCrypt and why another website about US common law</title><link>https://benjipeng.github.io/common-law/post/LexCrypt%20and%20why%20another%20website%20about%20US%20common%20law.html</link><description>The intersection of technology and law has never been more fascinating, particularly when we observe the parallels between scientific methodology and legal reasoning. As scientists and engineers, we've discovered that the systematic approach we use in solving complex technical problems shares remarkable similarities with legal analysis and precedent-based reasoning in common law. Both domains require meticulous attention to detail, logical progression of thought, and the ability to build upon established foundations while adapting to new circumstances.&#13;
&#13;
Recent advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) and Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have revolutionized our ability to process and understand information. With advanced models like GPT-4, GPT-o1, and Google Gemini Pro demonstrating unprecedented capabilities in understanding context, analyzing complex documents, and drawing meaningful connections, we stand at the threshold of a new era in legal accessibility. &#13;
&#13;
We have been inspired us to create LexCrypt, a platform where we bridge the gap between traditional legal knowledge and modern technological capabilities.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://benjipeng.github.io/common-law/post/LexCrypt%20and%20why%20another%20website%20about%20US%20common%20law.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>